Coordonnées

762714888 (Mobile) ryhow99@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ mouhammadouod (LinkedIn) github.com/MouhammadouOD (Portfolio)

Principales compétences

React.js Next.js

TypeScript

Languages

Anglais (Professional Working)
Arabe (Limited Working)
Français (Full Professional)

Mouhammadou Oury Diallo

Fullstack JavaScript developer

Arrondissement de Dakar-Plateau, Région de Dakar, Sénégal

Résumé

I am a Software Engineer specialized in Web Development with JavaScript.My deep passion consist of building Web applications with friendly User Interface to improve productivity and bring solutions to business or industry.I'am currently working at OMEDEMA as a FullStack Developer to build a Match Marketing Platform that help International companies to find right partners in Africa. I also provides course as a FullStack Js instructor at Gomycode, a school that form young generation about new technologies.

Skills: ReactJs, NextJs, TypeScript, TailwindCss, NodeJs, Express, Rest-API, MongoDB, back-end, Wordpress, AWS.

Expérience

OMEDEMA

Full-stack Developer septembre 2021 - Present (1 an 6 mois)

France

- Work on Omedema's Landing Page
- Develop the landing Page using NextJS, TailwindCss, TypeScript, NodeJS.
- Make Unit tests for all components using Jest, react-testing-library, Enzyme.
- Write integration tests with Jest and Enzyme.
- Work on Omedema's Platform-app
- build forms for signing in the platform with react-hook-forms.
- build the entire live-chat using Socket-io to put in place the real-time chat feature.

Page 1 of 3

• install the State management feature for the app with Redux-toolkit.

GOMYCODE

9 mois

Web development instructor juillet 2022 - février 2023 (8 mois) Région de Dakar, Sénégal

- Support the students in their learning.
- Assist them in their learning, projects and answer their questions.
- help them achieve FullStack JavaScript developer skills.

Full Stack Js instructor

juin 2022 - septembre 2022 (4 mois)

Région de Dakar, Sénégal

- Supported the students in their learning.
- I've assisted them in their projects and answer their questions.

SEN IT TECHNOLOGY

Full Stack Developer

juin 2021 - septembre 2021 (4 mois)

Dakar, Senegal

- Built an inventory and Sales Management Application with the MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, ReactJS, NodeJs) and Bootstrap.
- This project was the subject of my thesis for my university diploma of technology in computer engineering.
- I got a mark of 16/20 from the jury.

Hopital Regional de Ourossogui

J2Ee Developer

juin 2020 - septembre 2020 (4 mois)

Ourossogui, Matam, Sénégal

- Hospital Management app for patients and medical records monitoring
- •built Beans classes (User, Appointment, Medicine, PatientsRecord, Consultation)
- •Implement DAO classes for all Beans
- •Write sql database script to setup all tables and fill in default informations
- built servlets for every JSP(Java Server Pages)
- •built JSP for every page of the application

Formation

École Supérieure Polytechnique de Dakar

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering · (2021 - août 2022)

GOMYCODE

Fullstack javascript certification, Programmation informatique · (juin 2021 - octobre 2021)

Ecole supérieure polytechnique de Dakar University Diploma of Technology in Computer Engineering, Informatique · (2018 - juillet 2021)

LYCEE SEYDINA LIMAMOULAYE
BACCALAUREAT, SÉRIE S1 · (octobre 2014 - juillet 2017)